metropolis.co.jp 2004-10-10

# directory.japantoday.com: Japan's No 1 business directory

**JAPAN TODAY PRIVACY POLICY**

**Effective** **September 1, 2002**

Your privacy is important to us. This notice explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This notice is available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Registration information**  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Japan Today (including Metropolis) websites during registration and when ordering services. The types of personal information we collect includes: 

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
Company  
Credit/Debit Card Information  
IP address

Currently, we keep registration information for different parts of the site in different databases. To allow users a single login for all Japan Today sites we will unify these databases in the near future.

**Server log information**  
Japan Today also uses webtrendslive.com, an external page-tracking service. Webtrendslive.com's privacy policy is [here](http://www.webtrendslive.com/wtl_marcom/privacy_policy.htm#priv2). This service tracks total number of page views and country of origin. This information is used to find out which parts of a site are most popular and to provide aggregate marketing information to clients.  Detail information is not disclosed to third-parties. 

Japan Today may also records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address and the page you request.   

**Use of information**  
We do not sell your personal information to third-parties, however we may send mails to users on behalf of third-parties. Users may opt-out of these mailings. 

We only accept third party mailings that we feel are of genuine interest to our users. We will not send mails for casinos, work-at-home programs, pornography or other generic spam.

We send all registered users regular email updates on the Japan Today system. Users may opt-out of these mailings.

We send all registered users email when new Japan Today services are launched. Users may opt-out of these mailings.

We do not keep email addresses entered in the send-article-to-a-friend system.

 **Japan Today email newsletter**  
This service is run through Yahoo Groups. Please refer to the [Yahoo Groups Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/)

We use emails from this system to send system messages, to introduce new products, and to send mails on behalf of third-parties. Users may opt out of these mailings. 

**Discussions**  
To register for Japan Today discussions you are required to provide a valid email address.

We track the IP address of every posting on Japan Today discussions.

We remove personally identifiable postings where necessary.

 **Japan Today News Poll**  
No personal information is collected for this poll.

 **Surveys  
**We conduct surveys on behalf of third-parties. Any information collected will be used by third-parties in their marketing efforts.

We ask all third-parties to use information gathered in surveys responsibly. 

However, we have no control over how the third-party uses the information collected. 

**Cookies**   
We write two types of cookies

a) Registration cookie: allows user to access Japan Today without logging in  
b) Advertising cookie: allows an individual ad to appear on each page.  

**Data security**   
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

All online credit card transactions are performed only on secure servers through a secure SSL connection.  
Credit Card information for recurring payments is not stored on our public servers.

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information

 **Legal disclosure**  
Japan Today reserves the right to reveal registration information pursuant to a valid subpoena or court order.

We reserve the right to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Japan Today's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

 **Changes to this policy**  
Japan Today may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the email address specified in your Japan Today account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

We will transfer information about you if Japan Today is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

 **Accessing or correcting Your information**  
At any time, you may review or update your personal information by logging in to Japan Today or by contacting us at: [support@japantoday.com](mailto:billing@swanksoft.com) To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**Contact**  
Please do not hesitate to contact us at [support@japantoday.com](mailto:support@japantoday.com) if you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy.
